<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>Open Research Notebook</title>
    <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook</link>
    <description>Open Research Notebook</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Loading-Audio-DAEA</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Loading-Audio-DAEA.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 12:51:49 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Loading Audio into DAEA 1. Open aa-sites-popup.csv 2. After `link` add a comma and `audio` 3. For each `audio` column, add audio html tags: `audio src="test.mp3" controls preload/audio` For audio source, if you are hosting a local file, make sure to complete the path fully. For instance, if your audio...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Audio in pykwiki</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Audio in pykwiki.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 12:29:28 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Below is an audio clip of me working, with talking around the last minute. Simply paste this code into nvALT, filling in the source with your audio (as a file or URL) `audio src="your source" controls preload/audio` audio src="http://bladesrob.com/soundscape-audio/151110_0082.wav" controls preload/audio...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note.3</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.3.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 16:14:58 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Have to use local js and css files for twine package Usually, we see historians as people who go out, gather information, stories, etc., and bring it back all in to tell a story. That somehow, the product is what counts. And I am not denying the interpretive power and...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.html</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 13:59:10 EST</pubDate>
        <description>pembroke fb group is a serious community around which people organize their lives and memory. I am not able to take that away from them. what is my relation to memory? Obviously immediately nana; she is like baba, helping me so much by her own volition - but what else?...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note.6</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.6.html</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 10:12:03 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Why Use the interface at all? Not only do you learn more about your machine, but you begin to master an integral way to access files. You'll have noticed that with the cat command, you see the beginning of regex. In the next lesson, Milligan and Baker go over this...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note.5</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.5.html</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 16:01:37 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Open Access: how to make information consumable and geared towards stakeholders, answering their needs, vs. presenting information in a way I would like to. There is a huge digital negotiation anticipating platforms in a public history project. It is public history because it is built taking into account the stakeholders....</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note.2</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.2.html</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 11:28:50 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Zotero in my project: have to clip from newspapers.com to make it available, yet then it is only what I have clipped. Stability of online urls and IPs is uncertain....</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Untitled Note.1</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Untitled Note.1.html</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 10:03:45 EST</pubDate>
        <description>I can see Sparql being used for some really cool visualizations to see patterns; however, it is only as good as its database...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Pandoc</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Pandoc.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 11:43:13 EST</pubDate>
        <description>...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>WGET-and-Data-Mining-the-Internet-Archive</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/WGET-and-Data-Mining-the-Internet-Archive.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2016 11:41:23 EST</pubDate>
        <description> Wget There are other methods to download stuff on the internet. What makes wget good? Wow... you can do so much with such a tiny little command. The best aspect is `-r` or recursive retrieval which follows links from a website (to a certain depth). Mine all the things!...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Leaflet-Storymap-Audio</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Leaflet-Storymap-Audio.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 10:15:33 EST</pubDate>
        <description>I wracked my brain for a whole day but I did it! I added audio to Jack Dougherty's [leaflet storymap](https://github.com/JackDougherty/leaflet-storymap). To do this: 1. Open your terminal and `cd` to the `leaflet-storymap` directory 2. Make a new folder for audio files `mkdir audio` 3. Add your audio files to this...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Welcome-HIST5702!</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Welcome-HIST5702!.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 15:00:14 EST</pubDate>
        <description> Happy to Start HIST5702! I love GitHub! It is easy to push content to it. I also love the fact that I can run a free website from your account. I currently run [my own site](http://bladesrob.com) with [Reclaim Hosting](http://reclaimhosting.com/). However, I also run my grad work at [rblades.github.io](http://rblades.github.io) (with...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Understanding-Digital-Tools</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Understanding-Digital-Tools.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:45 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Design has sound; rougher designs will have harsher sounds than warm ones. I aim to mix things up Multimedia helps to create a complex perceptual environment rather than just one focused on sounds (Ingold critiques the divide of the senses that soundscapes promote, even unintentionally)....</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-10</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-10.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:42 EST</pubDate>
        <description>We are not just distant reading sources - we are distant reading the historicity of these digital tools and the practices and methods entangled in them through years of habit and process. We are taking our critiques into the digital realm to offer Sarah Durrant to historical care and attention...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-9</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-9.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:41 EST</pubDate>
        <description>The digital is an augmented reality in Stuart Eve's terms - that is, a user works in the "real world while visually receiving additional computer generated or modelled information." But even non-digital historical work is an augmented reality in itself since we approach the past by layering sources and drawing...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-6</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-6.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:35 EST</pubDate>
        <description>The current collection of digital material that forms the basis for most of our research is composed of the maudlin leavings of rich dead white men (and some rich dead white women). Until we get around to including the non-cannonical, the non-Western, the non-textual and the non-elite, we are unlikely...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-5</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-5.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:32 EST</pubDate>
        <description>There is an element of augmented reality in the layers of these digital sources. A source code is emulated as an interface. It is easy, then, to get caught up in the habit of clicking and getting. Digital humanists must learn the dirty art of doing the work themselves, least...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-4</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-4.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:31 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Everything has a history. As Hitchcock notes, DH historicity = ideas of codebreaking and 'cracking' from the 20th century. We fall into those same tropes and traps. In my own work on sound studies, this is particularly true of my map: listening has a history formed by years of recorded...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-3</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-3.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:29 EST</pubDate>
        <description>Confronted by people happy to define a point on the earth's surface as three simple numbers, and to claim that it was always so, was a shock. This is not to say that the archaeologists were being naïve, far from it, but that having been trained up as a text...</description>
    </item>    
    
    <item>
        <title>Hitchcock-2</title>
        <link>http://rblades.github.io//open-notebook/Hitchcock-2.html</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 14:20:26 EST</pubDate>
        <description>It feels to me as if our practise as humanists and historians is being driven by the technology, rather than being served by it. We are being driven by it only if we refuse to understand its structure and purpose and then critique it and our understanding of it. Hitchcock...</description>
    </item>    
    
</channel>
</rss>